

SEBASTIAN PRADO

FULL STACK DEVELOPER JR/ AGRICULTURAL ENGINEER

SUMMARY

Former agricultural engineer turned Full stack web developer..

With 8 years of experience in improving crop production efficiency and solving agricultural challenges, I bring an interesting perspective to full stack web development. My background in agricultural engineering has honed my problem-solving skills, attention to detail, and ability to optimize processes. A bit obsessed with always learning new things.

TECHNOLOGIES

- HTML.
- CSS.
- JavaScript (ES6+).
- Node + Express.
- React + Redux.
- MySQL and MongoDB.
- Git.
- Insomnia

IDIOMS

- Spanish (Native C2).
- English (Superior C1 / PTE 85pts / CAE band 8).
- Portuguese (Competent)

CONTACT



+61 455 234 514 (Aus).



sebastian.pradomelesi@gmail.com.



@SebaPrado



sebaprado-personal-portfolio.vercel.app

EDUCATION

Coding Bootcamp - Full Stack Web Developer

Hack Academy | Jan 2024 - Apr 2024

Full-time educational course, extremely hands-on and intensive.

Total hours: more than 600 hs.

Technologíes: HTML, CSS, React, Node, MongoDB, MySQL y Git. Final project: e-commerce site (https://equalvision.vercel.app/).

Front-End course

Hack Academy | Nov 2020

Total hours: 60 hs.

Technologíes: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap.

Agricultural engineering Bachelor degree.

UDELAR University | 2009 - 2013

100% completed.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Web Developer.

Equal vision e-commerce | Apr 2024 - May 2024

- Database creation
- UX/UI design.

Agricultual engineer.

Yaloak estate, Vic. Australia | Jun 2021- Ago 2023

- prescision agridulture technitian.
- crop advisory.

Private agricultural advisory | Jun 2019 - Oct 2020

• Developing Sustainable Dairy Land Plans, focused on the calculation of soil loss related to hidric erosion.

Maize seed chamber, Mdeo, Uruguay | Mar 2018 - Mar 2019

- Elaborating proposals to reduce the impact of agricultural activity on the contamination of water courses.
- Controlling agricultural practices related to IRM (Insect resistance management)

REFERENCES

Programming

• Facundo Irazusta - Hack Academy

Whatsapp: +598 96 110 111

Australia

• Rob Binks - General manager . Yaloak Ag Co

Ph: + 61 428548511

• Stuart Booth - General manager. Caldermeade farm

Ph: + 61 435779748